Question your humanity
5th Passenger is a science fiction, tv movie film directed by Scotty Baker.
Set in the aftermath of an oppressive class war, a pregnant officer aboard an escape pod must struggle to survive with her
remaining crew when a mysterious and vicious life form attacks, determined to become the dominant species.
Langdon, played by Doug Jones.
Franklin, played by Tim Russ.
Alana, played by Marina Sirtis.
Myers, played by Armin Shimerman.
Thea, played by Mindy Robinson.
Li, played by David Lim.
Michael David Rosenberg (born 17 May 1984), better known by his stage name
Passenger, is an English indie folk singer, songwriter and musician.
From the 2000s, Rosenberg fronted a band by the same name; he opted to keep the
Passenger moniker for his solo work after the band dissolved.
Rosenberg is best known for the 2012 song "Let Her Go", which topped the charts in
16 countries and accumulated more than 3.9 billion views on YouTube.
Because Rosenberg was based in Australia at the time of release (and the clip itself was filmed at the
Factory Theatre in Marrickville), it is the most-viewed Australian YouTube video ever.
In 2014, the song was nominated for the Brit Award for British Single of the Year, and he
received the British Academy's Ivor Novello Award for Most Performed Work.
A prolific singer-songwriter, Rosenberg has released 14 studio albums to
date: one with the band Passenger, and 13 as a solo artist.
The most recent of these, Birds That Flew and Ships
That Sailed, was released in April 2022.
The tone is thought_provoking.